<intro>
	<buttons>
		<next><![CDATA[NEXT]]></next>
		<transcript><![CDATA[TRANSCRIPT]]></transcript>
	</buttons>
	<caption>
    <![CDATA[Hello, my name is Katherin Nukk-Freeman, and I'm one of the creators of the training program you are about to engage in. I've been a practicing employment law attorney for over twenty years, and have spent the majority of my career helping employers comply with the many employment laws that govern the workplace. I've also been involved in defending numerous employment lawsuits, and I can tell you from those experiences that it's in everyone's best interest, the employers and all employees, to do whatever you can to get up to speed to take steps to prevent harassment and discrimination in the workplace. Why is that? Because harassment and discrimination at work is costly.<br><br> 
First of all, it decreases morale and productivity in the workplace amongst all employees. Secondly, it's distracting and will take you away from focusing on your job and doing your job well. In addition to that, it can be incredibly embarrassing, especially if you're the one who's named on a publicly filed complaint, or worse yet, the news hits the papers. And lastly, because employers take these types of harassment and discrimination complaints so seriously. I've seen many complaints negatively impact the careers and professional lives of employees.<br><br>
So why are you taking this training? The bottom line is that your employer is committed to creating the best possible work environment for all employees, and preventing harassment and discrimination is essential to that goal. In addition, this training is important to you for a number of reasons.<br><br>
First, you can positively or negatively impact your work environment. It's also important for you to know where the current line is drawn between appropriate conduct in the workplace, and conduct which may in fact violate your organizations workplace harassment and discrimination policies. If you don't know where that line is drawn, you can unknowingly cross it, and as a result, someone could file a complaint or make a complaint about your conduct. If someone makes a complaint about you, your organization has a responsibility to take those complaints seriously, and as a result, the backlash of the complaint could negatively impact both your reputation and your career path.<br><br>
If you supervise or manage employees in the workplace, the stakes are even higher. First, as manager, you are responsible for maintaining a productive work environment. But beyond that, from a legal perspective as a frontline manager, you're responsible for preventing harassment and discrimination in the workplace. In fact, depending upon which state you work in, you could be held personally liable for the outcome in any harassment or discrimination lawsuit. What does that mean? That means at the end of the day, you could be responsible for a portion of a judgment entered against you and/or your organization. 
This training, which you are about to engage in, will help sensitize you to the issues related to harassment and discrimination in the workplace. It will help you make better decisions, so that you can more positively impact your work environment, and your professional career.

]]></caption>
	<video>../../content/theater/intro.mp4</video>
</intro>