<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<harassment>
  <contentRoot>../../content/sexual/</contentRoot>
  <global>
    <of><![CDATA[OF]]></of>
    <meterheader><![CDATA[Success Meter]]></meterheader>
  </global>
  <buttons>
    <next>Next</next>
    <policy>Definition</policy>
    <close>Close</close>
    <agree>Accept</agree>
    <ignore>Ignore</ignore>
    <tryagain>Try Again</tryagain>
  </buttons>
  <advisors>
    <advisor id="1"><![CDATA[advisor1.png]]></advisor>
    <advisor id="2"><![CDATA[advisor2.png]]></advisor>
    <advisor id="3"><![CDATA[advisor3.png]]></advisor>
    <advisor id="4"><![CDATA[advisor4.png]]></advisor>
  </advisors>
  <meter>
    <title><![CDATA[CUMULATIVE PERFORMANCE METER]]></title>
    <level><![CDATA[Exceeds Expectations]]></level>
    <level><![CDATA[Meets Expectations]]></level>
    <level><![CDATA[Needs Improvement]]></level>
  </meter>
  <introvideo>
    <vidnext><![CDATA[NEXT]]></vidnext>
    <video>../../content/sexual/video/M2-introvideo-GOLD.mp4</video>
  </introvideo>
  <intro>
    <page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="133" width="410">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
      <header />
      <body><![CDATA[The next few screens will help you better understand and identify what sexual harassment looks like in the workplace and what role you can play when you witness it.]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="100" width="700">
      <background scale="1" x="-25" y="-25" animate="true" />
      <header><![CDATA[What is Sexual Harassment? FOR ALLEN DEVELOPMENT]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[Sexual harassment is a form of sex discrimination and includes any unwelcome conduct which is of a sexual nature, or which is directed at someone because of their sex.
				It is considered sexual harassment when:
				<br><ul>
				<li>Such conduct unreasonably interferes with an individual's work performance, or creates an intimidating, hostile or offensive work environment, even if the reporting individual is not the target of the sexual harassment;</li>
				<li>Such conduct is made either explicitly or implicitly a term or condition of employment; or</li>
				<li>Submission to or rejection of such conduct is used as the basis for an employment decision affecting an individual's employment.</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="img/9.jpg" x="0" y="191" width="370">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
      <header><![CDATA[Unwelcome Behavior]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[Welcome behavior can become unwelcome behavior at any point.   What starts off as welcome behavior (consensual joking) can cross a line and become unwelcome behavior.  
				Consent can be revoked at any time and the perpetrator must immediately stop the unwanted behavior.]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="0" width="1000" height="400" nextX="810" html="./legal.html">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="0" width="1000" height="400" nextX="810" html="./legalpoint.html">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
    </page>
    <page background="img/11.jpg" x="540" y="26" width="474" height="400">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
      <header><![CDATA[Two Types of Sexual Harassment]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[<div style="font-size:17px;">
				<div style="padding:0 0 5px 0;">There are two main types of sexual harassment:</div>
			<div>
			<span class="bold" style="font-weight: bold;">Hostile Work Environment </span>
			<br>
			Sexual harassment occurs when unwelcome comments or conduct based on sex unreasonably interfere with your work performance or create an intimidating, hostile, or offensive work environment. Someone may experience sexual harassment even if the offensive conduct was not aimed directly at him or her.
			<br><br>
			<span class="bold" style="font-weight: bold;">Quid Pro Quo (Latin for "this for that")</span>
			<br>
			Sexual harassment is when someone conditions a job, promotion, or other work benefit on submission to sexual advances or other conduct based on sex.</div></div>]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="img/11.jpg" x="534" y="50" width="474" height="400">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true" />
      <header><![CDATA[Is Sexual Harassment Limited to Men Harassing Women?]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[No! It may be considered unlawful sexual harassment when:<br><ul>
				<li>Men sexually harass women</li>
				<li>Women sexually harass men</li>
				<li>Men sexually harass men </li>
				<li>Women sexually harass women</li>
				<li>An individual of any gender, sexual orientation, gender identity or gender expression sexually harasses another individual of any gender, sexual orientation, gender identity or gender expression</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
  </intro>
  <examples>
    <next><![CDATA[NEXT]]></next>
    <header><![CDATA[Examples of Sexual Harassment]]></header>
    <instructions><![CDATA[You are about to practice identifying sexual harassment when you see it. Click each image to see several examples. You'll  be able to access these examples during the activity if you need help.]]></instructions>
    <example>
      <img src="3_1.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Inappropriate emails/text messages </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_2.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Showing another employee inappropriate websites or videos with sexual content </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexually demeaning or pornographic publications or displays, including on workplace computers or cell phones </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_3.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Sexual remarks about a person's body, clothing or appearance </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexual teasing, jokes, remarks or questions  </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_4.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Patting, pinching, hugging, kissing or other unwanted touching</li>
				<br>
				<li>Leering or ogling </li>
				<br>
				<li>Inappropriate sexual advances </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_5.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Damaging a person's workstation or otherwise sabotaging job performance because of their sex </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexually oriented gestures, noises, remarks, jokes or comments about a person's sexuality or sexual experience</li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_6.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Pressure for dates</li>
				<br>
				<li>Posting sexually explicit comments on social media sites </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
    <example>
      <img src="3_7.jpg" />
      <label />
      <feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Solicitation of sexual favors or other sexually related behavior by promise of rewards</li>
				<br>
				<li>Retaliating for refusing to engage in a sexual relationship</li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
    </example>
  </examples>
  <intro2>
    <!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="900">
			<background scale="0.68" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Gender-based terms]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA["Gender Expression" means a person's gender-related appearance or behavior, or the perception of such appearance or behavior, whether or not stereotypically associated with the person's sex assigned at birth.<br><br>
			"Gender Identity" means each person's internal understanding of their gender, or the perception of a person's gender identity, which may include male, female, a combination of male and female, neither male nor female, and/or a gender different from the person's sex assigned at birth, or transgender.<br><br>
			"Sex Stereotype" includes, but is not limited to, an assumption about a person's appearance or behavior, gender roles, gender expression, or gender identity, or about an individual's ability or inability to perform certain kinds of work based on a myth, social expectation, or generalization about the individual's sex.<br><br>
			"Transgender" is a general term that refers to a person whose gender identity differs from the person's sex assigned at birth. A transgender person may or may not have a gender expression that is different from the social expectations of the sex assigned at birth. A transgender person may or may not identify as "transsexual."]]></body>
		</page> -->
    <!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="700">
			<background scale="0.68" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[What does transitioning mean?]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA["Transitioning" is a process some transgender people go through to begin living as the gender with which they identify, rather than the sex assigned to them at birth. This process may include, but is not limited to, changes in name and pronoun usage, facility usage, participation in employer-sponsored activities (e.g. sports teams, team-building projects, or volunteering), or undergoing hormone therapy, surgeries, or other medical procedures.<br><br>
			"Social Transitioning" involves a process of socially aligning one's gender with the internal sense of self (e.g. changes in name and pronoun, bathroom facility usage, participation in activities like sports teams).<br><br>
			"Physical Transitioning" refers to medical treatments an individual may undergo to physically align their body with internal sense of self (e.g. hormone therapies or surgical procedures).]]></body>
		</page> -->
    <!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="85" width="1000" html="examples.html">
			<background scale="0.55" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
		</page> -->
    <page background="img/sexual_har_intro.jpg" x="0" y="130" width="838" html="examplescontext.html">
      <background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false" />
    </page>
    <page background="img/10.jpg" x="461" y="40" width="540" html="examplestechnology.html">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false" />
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="110" width="700">
      <background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[From Bystander to Upstander:  Combatting Workplace Sexual Harassment FOR ALLEN DEVELOPEMENT]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[Every employee should feel empowered to speak up and advocate for respect, inclusion and a civil workplace. Imagine a workplace where people took action to stop potential acts of sexual harassment by disrupting offensive conduct or publicly supporting those who have been mistreated.]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="700">
      <background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[From Bystander to Upstander:  Combatting Workplace Sexual Harassment FOR ALLEN DEVELOPEMENT]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[<span class="bold" style="font-size:24px">Upstanders</span> "speak up" in the workplace when they witness sexual harassment or other inappropriate conduct.
			<br><br>
			<span class="bold" style="font-size:24px">Bystanders</span> take no action.]]></body>
    </page>
    <!--
				<page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="615">
					<background scale="0.75" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
					<header><![CDATA[Why Some Bystanders Fail to Act]]></header>
					<body><![CDATA[<div style="width: 507px;">It may be a natural inclination to avoid getting involved.  Some of the most common reasons bystanders often fail to act are:
						<ul>
							<li>A belief that someone else will act</li>
							<li>Uncertainty about what to do</li>
							<li>Peer pressure</li>
							<li>Fear of conflict or damage to relationships</li>
							<li>The assumption that it's not their place</li>
						</ul></div>
						]]></body>
				</page>
		-->
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="105" width="1000" height="200" html="failtoact.html">
      <background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false" />
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="105" width="1000" height="200" html="strategies.html">
      <background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false" />
    </page>
    <page background="img/16.jpg" x="489" y="100" width="528">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[Strategies an Upstander Can Take in Response to Harassment]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[There may be times when you are unable to respond to an incident in the moment.  In those cases, there are actions you can take after the fact.
				<ul>
					<li>Privately support the target of behavior</li>
					<li>Talk privately with the inappropriate actor whose words or actions were offensive</li>
					<li>Report the incident to a person of authority if there is any doubt</li>
				</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
  </intro2>
  <instructions>
    <slide><![CDATA[In the following activity, you will encounter four situations. You'll meet advisors who will give you advice on what to do. It's up to you to decide who to listen to and why.]]></slide>
    <slide><![CDATA[Here are your advisors. After watching a video, click each advisor to read their suggestions and choose IGNORE until you are sure you are ready to ACCEPT the best advice. Remember, you can only choose to accept the advice of ONE person, so choose carefully.]]></slide>
    <slide><![CDATA[Here is your Cumulative Performance Meter. When you choose correctly, the meter will increase. If you choose the best possible answer, the meter will increase by even more. Your goal is to push the meter all the way to the top by the end of the exercise. Remember, if your performance in these situations does not meet expectations, you will be required to retake the exercise.]]></slide>
    <persistent><![CDATA[Click each advisor below to review his or her advice. Choose IGNORE until you decide which advisor gives the BEST advice. You must accept one advisor's recommendation to move to the next situation.]]></persistent>
  </instructions>
  <situation><![CDATA[Situation #]]></situation>
  <theadvisors><![CDATA[The Advisors]]></theadvisors>
  <advisorPrompt><![CDATA[Is this the one piece of advice you'd like to choose?]]></advisorPrompt>
  <scenario id="1">
    <video>../../content/sexual/video/AMELIA-A2.1.mp4</video>
    <background><![CDATA[It’s been great catching up. I guess there’s just one more thing I wanted to mention before I go. It’s kind of awkward to even say, but Doreen in technology asked me out on a date last week. I let her know that I wasn’t interested, and she seemed to take it OK. I’m just concerned about things getting awkward from here. We still have to work together.]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[It seems like Cassandra has a bias against Doreen because of her sexual orientation. I think her issue is more with Doreen being gay than her invite. Since sexual orientation is a protected characteristic, you should bring this situation to the attention of the appropriate personnel here.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[Cassandra doesn’t appear to be showing bias and should not be accused of any just for sharing a situation that made her uncomfortable.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[It’s too bad she’s uncomfortable. But just tell her to keep acting as she normally would. At this point, if Doreen is leaving her alone, there is not much you can do.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[It’s technically correct that Cassandra should carry on as usual, but remember to show empathy and let her know what to do if Doreen persists.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Oh no. You’ll need to talk with Doreen and let her know that she was way out of line.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[It is not appropriate to talk with Doreen at this point. She didn’t appear to cross a line of inappropriate behavior.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[Thank Cassandra for letting you know and tell her you’ll keep an eye on the situation. Going forward she should just maintain a business-as-usual relationship. But encourage Cassandra to tell you if Doreen continues paying her unwanted attention or asking her out, and you’ll be sure the situation is addressed.]]></advice>
    </advisor>
  </scenario>
  <scenario id="2">
    <video>../../content/sexual/video/AMELIA-A2.1.mp4</video>
    <background><![CDATA[Hey. I want to get your thoughts on something. I know that Margaux is the next logical choice for a promotion on our team. I mean, she does great work and probably deserves it the most. But if I put her in that role, we’d have to travel together a lot. I can tell you my wife would not be happy about that! I think it would be better for all of us if I just promote Andy instead. He’s done good work since he started, and we’d work and travel really well together.]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[That’s tough. Let Ari know that you get his predicament. A lot of spouses might respond the same way. It’s risky these days for men and women to work too closely together.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[You should explain to Ari that making a decision based on Margaux’s gender that negatively impacts her career is against the organization’s policy and the law.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[It sounds like the only reason Ari doesn’t want to promote Margaux is because she’s a woman.  Making a decision like that based on gender would go against our organization’s policy and the law. He should review the role’s criteria and promote the most deserving candidate, which seems to be Margaux. If she’s best suited, Ari can then meet with the appropriate people here for guidance with his travel concerns.]]></advice>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[From what Ari is telling you, if he chooses not to give the promotion to Margaux, that could be considered sex discrimination.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[The advice you accepted is accurate, but it would be more helpful to give Ari some guidance on how to handle the situation.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Tell Ari not to worry about it. Margaux probably wouldn’t even want a job that required that much travel. She’s got young kids. And if Ari offers her the position that requires travel, it will likely put her in a difficult position.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[It is not appropriate to make assumptions about someone’s career goals and abilities based on their gender or family status.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
  </scenario>
  <!-- <scenario id="3">
		<background><![CDATA[An important client calls and asks for his account to be managed by a male account representative instead of a female. He does not give any reason, but makes his preference for a "male" very clear. What should you do?]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender may be unlawful discrimination. Since unlawful harassment and discrimination are prohibited not only by employees and supervisors, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, etc., you should involve appropriate channels.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender may be unlawful discrimination, which is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Since the client is not your employee, there is really nothing you can do to remedy this situation. You should honor his request in the best interest of the business. You do not need to take further action.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Unlawful harassment is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors in addition to colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[The client did not explicitly say that he does not like working with women, so you cannot be sure that he is discriminating based on a protected characteristic. You do not need to involve appropriate channels at this time.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender would be unlawful discrimination, which is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Any time a client expresses a preference for one team member over another, this is a problem. You should involve appropriate channels in this situation.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[When a client's preference to work with one employee over another seems related to a protected characteristic, you need to involve appropriate channels.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
	</scenario> -->
  <scenario id="3">
    <video>../../content/sexual/video/AMELIA-A2.1.mp4</video>
    <background><![CDATA[Hi there. Do you have a second? Have you seen that social media account “Rate your co-worker”?  Apparently, that was started by Barry in the tech group. Some of the comments rate women in our office and even talk about their “attractiveness.” It’s making them really uncomfortable. What should you do?]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[Assure Anil you hadn’t heard and thank him for letting you know. Then ask how he found out it was Barry who started it. This is the kind of thing that should immediately be brought to the attention of the appropriate people. However, you don’t want to bring Barry’s name into it just based on rumor.]]></advice>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Let Anil know that you hadn’t heard about it and that you’ll be sure to report it right away.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[Ask more questions to learn if Anil has any firsthand information or if he is only reporting on rumors. You’ll want to share accurate information when you report to the appropriate personnel.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[That’s terrible. Our organization takes harassment and discrimination on social media seriously and will not tolerate it. Assure Anil you’ll talk with Barry right away and make sure he puts an end to this.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[Don’t accuse anyone of inappropriate behavior yet. So far, your information is based on rumor. Ask Anil more about what he knows, and then bring the information you have to the appropriate personnel.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[That’s pretty funny. There’s nothing you can do about a private social media account. You can just tell the women in the office not to look at the comments if it upsets them.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[This situation should not be viewed as funny but, if true, should be brought to the attention of the appropriate personnel to be addressed.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
  </scenario>
  <scenario id="4">
    <video>../../content/sexual/video/AMELIA-A2.1.mp4</video>
    <background><![CDATA[<span style="display:block;font-size:16px;line-height:1.1">Thanks for meeting with me. I just thought it was time I said something about Marcus. Soon after he started, Marcus gave me a nice compliment about what I was wearing that day. I was flattered. I even thanked him and told him that was so nice. But...since then, he started making comments about my outfits more frequently. This week he said, “Those pants really show off your figure.” It’s making me really uncomfortable, and I don’t know what to say to him. How do you see the situation?</span>]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Okay. Tell her you’ll escalate this internally and then see what happens.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[While your instinct to escalate this to the appropriate personnel is correct, you could offer a little more support and encouragement.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Let Jennifer know there’s no need to make too big a deal about this. You can go and talk with Marcus and make sure he doesn’t bother her anymore.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[In situations that may involve harassment and/or discrimination, involve the appropriate personnel to ensure everything is handled properly.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[If there was any actual harassment here, you should escalate the issue internally. But Marcus isn’t like that. Just reassure Jennifer that he doesn’t mean anything harmful with his comments.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[What you think of Marcus’s intentions doesn’t matter. If you’re made aware of possible harassment and/or discrimination, involve the appropriate personnel to ensure everything is handled properly.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[Let Jennifer know you’re sorry she’s been uncomfortable but you’re glad she came to talk with you. Marcus’s frequent comments about her appearance may have crossed a line. Tell her you’ll bring this up with the right people here and make sure the situation is addressed.]]></advice>
      <!-- <hint><![CDATA[David appears to be using his power to gain romantic or sexual favors, which is a form of sexual harassment.  If David wants to get to know Jessie better, he can offer a lunch during work hours and not at a romantic location.]]></hint> -->
    </advisor>
  </scenario>
  <!-- <scenario id="5">
    <background><![CDATA[<span style="display:block;font-size:23px;line-height:1.1">Charlotte has recently been promoted to work on Jeff's team.  Jeff has found that he has increasingly needed to work one on one with Charlotte. Charlotte is very attractive and everyone knows that Jeff is recently divorced. With all the talk about #METOO and men being accused of inappropriate behavior, Jeff is worried about how this new working relationship with Charlotte will look to the rest of the team and especially about being behind closed doors with Charlotte.  What should he do?</span>]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should keep his office door open whenever he has one on one meetings with anyone.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[While this may make Jeff more comfortable and he will not be singling Charlotte out as a woman, open door discussions may not always be practical and should not be necessary if Jeff conducts himself in a professional manner with all of his colleagues. ]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should ask to have Charlotte transferred to another team to avoid any awkwardness.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[This could be seen as discrimination based on Charlotte's gender.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should treat Charlotte the same as all other team members including with respect to his meeting protocol.  He cannot let his worry about workplace gossip impact his business relationships. However, if he hears untrue rumors about his relationship with Charlotte, he can have these rumors investigated by reporting them internally.]]></advice>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should call a team meeting and let everyone know that there is nothing romantic going on between him and Charlotte.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[This could be awkward for everyone, especially for Charlotte. ]]></hint>
    </advisor>
  </scenario> -->
  <feedback>
    <feedbacktitle><![CDATA[How did you do?]]></feedbacktitle>
    <low>
      <title1><![CDATA[You can do better.]]></title1>
      <page1><![CDATA[Based on the actions that you took (and did not take), here are some hints to guide you.
				[INJECT]
				When you are ready, click Try Again and take another look at these scenarios.]]></page1>
    </low>
    <medium>
      <title1><![CDATA[Nice Work!]]></title1>
      <page1><![CDATA[Based on the actions that you took (and did not take), here are the parts of the policy that you should carefully review.
				[INJECT]
				When you are ready, click Try Again and take another look at these scenarios. (Or, if you are satisfied with your rating, you could click Next.)]]></page1>
    </medium>
    <high>
      <title1><![CDATA[Excellent Work!]]></title1>
      <page1><![CDATA[Your competence in this area will go a long way toward creating a positive and inclusive work environment that is respectful and comfortable for everyone. You are a true role model in your organization.<br><br>Click Next to continue with this training.]]></page1>
    </high>
    <page background="img/22.jpg" x="0" y="-33" width="442" nextX="512">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[{TITLE}]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[{BODY 1}}]]></body>
    </page>
  </feedback>
  <outro>
    <page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="70" width="530" html="consider.html">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false" />
    </page>
    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="615">
      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[Remember...]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[As a supervisor, you are held to a heightened standard of behavior.
				<ul>
					<li>You are in a position of authority</li>
					<li>You are required to report any harassment that is reported to you or that you observe, even if no one is objecting to the harassment</li>
					<li>If you receive a report of, or are otherwise aware of, harassment you must promptly report it, even if you think the conduct is trivial or if the harassed individual asks you not to report it</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="93" width="850">
      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[So What's at Stake if You Don't Make the Right Decisions?]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[If you engage in sexual harassment or fail to follow your Organziation's anti-harassment and discrimination policy, your conduct could result in...<br><ul>
					<li>Discipline, up to and including termination</li>
	        <li>Damage to culture of inclusion and equal opportunities</li>
					<li>Loss of Organziation reputation</li>
					<li>Loss of your professional and personal reputation</li>
	        <li>Civil penalties</li>
					<li>Legal fees</li>
					<li>Monetary judgments</li>
	        <li>Criminal penalties</li>
					<li>Business interruptions and distractions leading to decreased employee engagement</li>
				</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
    <!--
	    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="120" width="570" height="300">
			<background scale="0.63" x="-335" y="-220" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[Let's take a look at one more scenario that will give you a chance to put your knowledge into action.
				<br><br>
			To progress through the scenario choose the box with the statment or question that best reflects your initial reaction to the situation described.]]></body>
		</page> -->
    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="362" y="200" width="638" heightOffset="220">
      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false" />
      <header />
      <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a better understanding of terminology and the types of protections afforded to transgender employees, let's take a look at one more scenario that will give you a chance to put your knowledge into practice.]]></body>
    </page>
    <!-- <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="362" y="200" width="638" heightOffset="220">
            <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
            <header><![CDATA[]]></header>
            <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a good sense for what types of behaviours consititute sexual harassment, let's examine one more situation.]]></body>
        </page> -->
  </outro>
  <outro1>
    <!-- <page background="img/12.jpg" x="500" y="82" width="530" heightOffset="220">
            <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
            <header><![CDATA[]]></header>
            <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a good sense for what types of behaviors consititute sexual harassment, let's examine one more situation.]]></body>
        </page> -->
  </outro1>
  <outro2>
    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="93" width="850">
      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[So What's at Stake if You Don't Make the Right Decisions? FOR ALLEN DEVELOPMENT]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[If you engage in sexual harassment or fail to follow your organization's anti-harassment and discrimination policy, your conduct could result in...<br><ul>
					<li>Discipline, up to and including termination</li>
	        <li>Damage to culture of inclusion and equal opportunities</li>
					<li>Loss of organization reputation</li>
					<li>Loss of your professional and personal reputation</li>
	        <li>Civil penalties</li>
					<li>Legal fees</li>
					<li>Monetary judgments</li>
	        <li>Criminal penalties</li>
					<li>Business interruptions and distractions leading to decreased employee engagement</li>
				</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
    <page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="45" width="464">
      <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false" />
      <header><![CDATA[Remember...]]></header>
      <body><![CDATA[As a supervisor, you are held to a heightened standard of behavior.
				<ul>
					<li>You are in a position of authority</li>
					<li>You are required to report any harassment that is reported to you or that you observe, even if no one is objecting to the harassment</li>
					<li>If you receive a report of, or are otherwise aware of, harassment you must promptly report it, even if you think the conduct is trivial or if the harassed individual asks you not to report it</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
    </page>
  </outro2>
</harassment>