<harassment>
	<contentRoot>../../content/sexual/</contentRoot>
	<global>
		<of><![CDATA[OF]]></of>
		<meterheader><![CDATA[Success Meter]]></meterheader>
	</global>

	<buttons>
		<next>Next</next>
		<policy>Definition</policy>
		<close>Close</close>
		<agree>Accept</agree>
		<ignore>Ignore</ignore>
		<tryagain>Try Again</tryagain>
	</buttons>

	<advisors>
		<advisor id="1"><![CDATA[advisor1.png]]></advisor>
		<advisor id="2"><![CDATA[advisor2.png]]></advisor>
		<advisor id="3"><![CDATA[advisor3.png]]></advisor>
		<advisor id="4"><![CDATA[advisor4.png]]></advisor>
	</advisors>

	<meter>
		<title><![CDATA[CUMULATIVE PERFORMANCE METER]]></title>
		<level><![CDATA[Exceeds Expectations]]></level>
		<level><![CDATA[Meets Expectations]]></level>
		<level><![CDATA[Needs Improvement]]></level>
	</meter>

	<introvideo>
        <vidnext><![CDATA[NEXT]]></vidnext>
        <video>../../content/sexual/video/M2-introvideo-GOLD.mp4</video>
    </introvideo>

	<intro>

		<page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="133" width="410">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[]]></header>
			<body>
          <![CDATA[The next few screens will help you better understand and identify what sexual harassment looks like in the workplace and what role you can play when you witness it. ]]></body>
		</page>

		<page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="100" width="700">
			<background scale="1" x="-25" y="-25" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[What is Sexual Harassment? FOR ALLEN DEVELOPMENT]]></header>
			<body>
          <![CDATA[Sexual harassment is a form of sex discrimination and includes any unwelcome conduct which is of a sexual nature, or which is directed at someone because of their sex.
				It is considered sexual harassment when:
				<br><ul>
				<li>Such conduct unreasonably interferes with an individual's work performance, or creates an intimidating, hostile or offensive work environment, even if the reporting individual is not the target of the sexual harassment;</li>
				<li>Such conduct is made either explicitly or implicitly a term or condition of employment; or</li>
				<li>Submission to or rejection of such conduct is used as the basis for an employment decision affecting an individual's employment.</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
		</page>

		<page background="img/9.jpg" x="0" y="191" width="370">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Unwelcome Behavior]]></header>
			<body>
          <![CDATA[Welcome behavior can become unwelcome behavior at any point.   What starts off as welcome behavior (consensual joking) can cross a line and become unwelcome behavior.  
Consent can be revoked at any time and the perpetrator must immediately stop the unwanted behavior. ]]></body>
		</page>

		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="0" width="1000" height="400" nextX="810" html="./legal.html">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
		</page>

		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="0" width="1000" height="400" nextX="810" html="./legalpoint.html">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
		</page>

    <page background="img/11.jpg" x="540" y="26" width="474" height="400">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Two Types of Sexual Harassment]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[
			<div style="font-size:17px;">
				<div style="padding:0 0 5px 0;">There are two main types of sexual harassment:</div>
			<div>
			<span class="bold" style="font-weight: bold;">Hostile Work Environment </span>
			<br>
			Sexual harassment occurs when unwelcome comments or conduct based on sex unreasonably interfere with your work performance or create an intimidating, hostile, or offensive work environment. Someone may experience sexual harassment even if the offensive conduct was not aimed directly at him or her.
			<br><br>
			<span class="bold" style="font-weight: bold;">Quid Pro Quo (Latin for "this for that")</span>
			<br>
			Sexual harassment is when someone conditions a job, promotion, or other work benefit on submission to sexual advances or other conduct based on sex.</div></div>
			]]></body>
		</page>

		<page background="img/11.jpg" x="534" y="50" width="474" height="400">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Is Sexual Harassment Limited to Men Harassing Women?]]></header>
			<body>
          <![CDATA[No! It may be considered unlawful sexual harassment when:<br><ul>
				<li>Men sexually harass women</li>
				<li>Women sexually harass men</li>
				<li>Men sexually harass men </li>
				<li>Women sexually harass women</li>
				<li>An individual of any gender, sexual orientation, gender identity or gender expression sexually harasses another individual of any gender, sexual orientation, gender identity or gender expression</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
		</page>

		</intro>

 		<examples>
		<next><![CDATA[NEXT]]></next>
		<header><![CDATA[Examples of Sexual Harassment]]></header>
		<instructions><![CDATA[You are about to practice identifying sexual harassment when you see it. Click each image to see several examples. You'll  be able to access these examples during the activity if you need help. ]]></instructions>

		<example>
			<img src="3_1.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Inappropriate emails/text messages </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_2.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Showing another employee inappropriate websites or videos with sexual content </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexually demeaning or pornographic publications or displays, including on workplace computers or cell phones </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_3.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Sexual remarks about a person's body, clothing or appearance </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexual teasing, jokes, remarks or questions  </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_4.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Patting, pinching, hugging, kissing or other unwanted touching</li>
				<br>
				<li>Leering or ogling </li>
				<br>
				<li>Inappropriate sexual advances </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_5.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Damaging a person's workstation or otherwise sabotaging job performance because of their sex </li>
				<br>
				<li>Sexually oriented gestures, noises, remarks, jokes or comments about a person's sexuality or sexual experience</li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_6.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Pressure for dates</li>
				<br>
				<li>Posting sexually explicit comments on social media sites </li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
		<example>
			<img src="3_7.jpg" />
			<label><![CDATA[]]></label>
			<feedback1><![CDATA[<ul style="list-style: square;line-height: 27px;font-size: 23px;">
				<li>Solicitation of sexual favors or other sexually related behavior by promise of rewards</li>
				<br>
				<li>Retaliating for refusing to engage in a sexual relationship</li>
			</ul>]]></feedback1>
		</example>
	</examples>




	<intro2>

		<!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="900">
			<background scale="0.68" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Gender-based terms]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA["Gender Expression" means a person's gender-related appearance or behavior, or the perception of such appearance or behavior, whether or not stereotypically associated with the person's sex assigned at birth.<br><br>
			"Gender Identity" means each person's internal understanding of their gender, or the perception of a person's gender identity, which may include male, female, a combination of male and female, neither male nor female, and/or a gender different from the person's sex assigned at birth, or transgender.<br><br>
			"Sex Stereotype" includes, but is not limited to, an assumption about a person's appearance or behavior, gender roles, gender expression, or gender identity, or about an individual's ability or inability to perform certain kinds of work based on a myth, social expectation, or generalization about the individual's sex.<br><br>
			"Transgender" is a general term that refers to a person whose gender identity differs from the person's sex assigned at birth. A transgender person may or may not have a gender expression that is different from the social expectations of the sex assigned at birth. A transgender person may or may not identify as "transsexual."]]></body>
		</page> -->

		<!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="700">
			<background scale="0.68" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[What does transitioning mean?]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA["Transitioning" is a process some transgender people go through to begin living as the gender with which they identify, rather than the sex assigned to them at birth. This process may include, but is not limited to, changes in name and pronoun usage, facility usage, participation in employer-sponsored activities (e.g. sports teams, team-building projects, or volunteering), or undergoing hormone therapy, surgeries, or other medical procedures.<br><br>
			"Social Transitioning" involves a process of socially aligning one's gender with the internal sense of self (e.g. changes in name and pronoun, bathroom facility usage, participation in activities like sports teams).<br><br>
			"Physical Transitioning" refers to medical treatments an individual may undergo to physically align their body with internal sense of self (e.g. hormone therapies or surgical procedures).]]></body>
		</page> -->





		<!-- <page background="SAME" x="0" y="85" width="1000" html="examples.html">
			<background scale="0.55" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
		</page> -->

		<page background="img/sexual_har_intro.jpg" x="0" y="130" width="838" html="examplescontext.html">
			<background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false"/>
		</page>

		<page background="img/10.jpg" x="461" y="40" width="540" html="examplestechnology.html">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
		</page>

		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="110" width="700">
			<background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[From Bystander to Upstander:  Combatting Workplace Sexual Harassment FOR ALLEN DEVELOPEMENT]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[Every employee should feel empowered to speak up and advocate for respect, inclusion and a civil workplace. Imagine a workplace where people took action to stop potential acts of sexual harassment by disrupting offensive conduct or publicly supporting those who have been mistreated.]]></body>
		</page>
		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="700">
			<background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[From Bystander to Upstander:  Combatting Workplace Sexual Harassment FOR ALLEN DEVELOPEMENT]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[<span class="bold" style="font-size:24px">Upstanders</span> "speak up" in the workplace when they witness sexual harassment or other inappropriate conduct.
			<br><br>
			<span class="bold" style="font-size:24px">Bystanders</span> take no action.]]></body>
		</page>
<!--
		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="615">
			<background scale="0.75" x="-755" y="-765" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Why Some Bystanders Fail to Act]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[<div style="width: 507px;">It may be a natural inclination to avoid getting involved.  Some of the most common reasons bystanders often fail to act are:
				<ul>
					<li>A belief that someone else will act</li>
					<li>Uncertainty about what to do</li>
					<li>Peer pressure</li>
					<li>Fear of conflict or damage to relationships</li>
					<li>The assumption that it's not their place</li>
				</ul></div>
				]]></body>
		</page>
 -->
		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="105" width="1000" height="200" html="failtoact.html">
			<background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false"/>
		</page>

		<page background="SAME" x="0" y="105" width="1000" height="200" html="strategies.html">
			<background scale="0.41" x="-845" y="-595" animate="false"/>
		</page>

		<page background="img/16.jpg" x="489" y="100" width="528">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Strategies an Upstander Can Take in Response to Harassment]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[There may be times when you are unable to respond to an incident in the moment.  In those cases, there are actions you can take after the fact.
				<ul>
					<li>Privately support the target of behavior</li>
					<li>Talk privately with the inappropriate actor whose words or actions were offensive</li>
					<li>Report the incident to a person of authority if there is any doubt</li>
				</ul>
				]]></body>
		</page>
	</intro2>

	<instructions>
		<slide><![CDATA[In the following activity, you will encounter five situations. You'll meet advisors who will give you advice on what to do. It's up to you to decide who to listen to and why.]]></slide>
		<slide><![CDATA[Here are your advisors. When the activity starts,  click each one to read their suggestions and choose IGNORE until you are sure you are ready to ACCEPT the best advice. Remember, you can only choose to accept the advice of ONE person, so choose carefully.]]></slide>
		<slide><![CDATA[Here is your Cumulative Performance Meter. When you choose correctly, the meter will increase. If you choose the best possible answer, the meter will increase by even more. Your goal is to push the meter all the way to the top by the end of the exercise. Remember, if your performance in these situations does not meet expectations, you will be required to retake the exercise.]]></slide>
		<persistent><![CDATA[Click each advisor below to review his or her advice. Choose IGNORE until you decide which advisor gives the BEST advice. You must accept one advisor's recommendation to move to the next situation.]]></persistent>
	</instructions>

	<situation><![CDATA[Situation #]]></situation>
	<theadvisors><![CDATA[The Advisors]]></theadvisors>
	<advisorPrompt><![CDATA[Is this the one piece of advice you'd like to choose?]]></advisorPrompt>
	<scenario id="1">
		<background><![CDATA[You are made aware of Snapchats sent from Lauren, a member of your team, to her co-worker John. The Snapchats contain a sexually explicit photo and graphic sexual language. However, you know that John and Lauren are close friends. You also know that John has sent Lauren similar messages in the past, and that they have both laughed about it. What should you do?]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[John and Lauren are friends with a history of this behavior. Since both have participated equally here, this does not constitute unlawful harassment. You do not need to take any further action.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Inappropriate Snapchats, text messages, and emails could be considered sexual harassment.  If you do not report such behavior when you witness it, you leave the organization and yourself at risk, even if both parties seem to be consenting. ]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Because Lauren is a woman and John is a man, this behavior is unacceptable. If they were both men or both women, you'd be fine.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Inappropriate Snapchats, text messages, and emails could be considered sexual harassment. It does not matter if this inappropriate communication is from a man to a woman or a woman to man, or if this communication is between employees of the same sex.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[This is a personal exchange between John and Lauren. If one of them complains about the situation it should be reported. But since neither of them has expressed any problem, you are not required to take any action at this time.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Inappropriate Snapchats, text messages, and emails, are considered sexual harassment if they relate to or are based on sex. If you do not report such behavior when you witness it, you leave the organization and yourself at risk. You cannot and should not wait for someone to complain before you take action. ]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[The sexually explicit nature of the photo and the language violate your organization's anti-harassment and discrimination policy, and it must be addressed.]]></advice>
		</advisor>
	</scenario>

	<scenario id="2">
		<background><![CDATA[Two men on your team who are at the same level and do not report to one another are dating. They intended to keep their relationship a secret, however, another employee noticed that they always have lunch together and eventually learned they were in a relationship. The employee who discovered this relationship expresses concern to you. What should you do?]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[The couple has violated your organization's anti-harassment and discrimination policy. You should report through your organization's reporting channels immediately.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Consenting adult relationships do not fall under the category of coercive behavior.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[Since the couple's behavior does not fall under the definition of harassment, you should feel comfortable letting your concerned employee know that there is no problem with his co-workers dating as long as they act professionally.]]></advice>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Since only one person has commented on this, you do not need to report anything at this time.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Some issues require escalation even if only one person has concerns. If a manager witnesses a reportable issue, the fact that no one has complained is also irrelevant.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Since relationship status is a protected characteristic, you should report the employee who expressed concern about the behavior to designated representatives.]]></advice>
<hint><![CDATA[Relationship status is not a protected characteristic.   Relationships in the workplace may impact others and managers should address any legitimate issues caused by such relationships immediately.]]></hint>
</advisor>
	</scenario>

	<!-- <scenario id="3">
		<background><![CDATA[An important client calls and asks for his account to be managed by a male account representative instead of a female. He does not give any reason, but makes his preference for a "male" very clear. What should you do?]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender may be unlawful discrimination. Since unlawful harassment and discrimination are prohibited not only by employees and supervisors, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, etc., you should involve appropriate channels.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender may be unlawful discrimination, which is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Since the client is not your employee, there is really nothing you can do to remedy this situation. You should honor his request in the best interest of the business. You do not need to take further action.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Unlawful harassment is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors in addition to colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[The client did not explicitly say that he does not like working with women, so you cannot be sure that he is discriminating based on a protected characteristic. You do not need to involve appropriate channels at this time.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[The client's request to work with an employee based on gender would be unlawful discrimination, which is prohibited not only by supervisors and employees, but also by clients, visitors, vendors, colleagues and supervisors.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Any time a client expresses a preference for one team member over another, this is a problem. You should involve appropriate channels in this situation.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[When a client's preference to work with one employee over another seems related to a protected characteristic, you need to involve appropriate channels.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
	</scenario> -->

	<scenario id="3">
		<background><![CDATA[Sally complains about Mark's repeated compliments about her clothing and appearance. Sally mentions that Mark frequently comments on specific parts of her body and how her outfits display them. Because of your personal interactions with Mark, you know that he is a happily married man, and you do not think he means to offend Sally or make her feel uncomfortable in any way when he compliments her. What should you do?]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[Your organization's anti-harassment and discrimination policy prohibits unwelcome comments about a person's appearance or clothing based on gender. Mark's intention behind complimenting Sally and the fact he is a happily married man does not matter. You could report this through the proper channels.]]></advice>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Intention is the key factor here. Since Mark does not mean for Sally to be offended, this does not constitute harassment. You do not need to report this.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[Harassing behavior needs to be addressed, even if the person making an unwelcome comment did not mean to offend Sally.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[You do not need to report this because you know Mark is a happily married man and likely didn't mean to offend.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[If anyone makes comments about a person that they (or someone else) could find offensive, then this could be considered harassment. The relationship status of the person making the comments is irrelevant.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="1">
			<advice><![CDATA[Tell Sally that she's right to feel uncomfortable and that you will monitor the situation.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[While you have correctly understood Sally's concerns, you are obligated to follow your organization's reporting channels here.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
	</scenario>

	<scenario id="4">
		<background><![CDATA[<span style="display:block;font-size:23px;line-height:1.1">Your colleague, Jessie, was approached by your senior manager, David, after her recent interview with him for a promotion. David suggested that Jessie join him one night after work for dinner.  He has chosen a romantic restaurant across the street from the office. He said it would be a good opportunity for him to get to know her better, especially as he is considering her for the promotion. Jessie has come to you for your perspective as she is uncertain whether to go out to dinner with David.  How do you see the situation?</span>]]></background>
		<advisor id="1" points="2">
			<advice><![CDATA[It is not appropriate for David to invite Jessie, a subordinate, on a date. Jessie could feel pressure to accept the date since David is considering her for promotion. It could appear that David is offering the promotion as quid pro quo for the date. ]]></advice>
			<!--<hint><![CDATA[Consensual romantic relationship is not considered unlawful harassment. However, your Organization may view a supervisor/employee consensual romantic relationship as a violation of other Organization Policies.]]></hint>-->
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="2" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[David and Jessie are two consenting adults. If Jessie is not interested in meeting David for dinner, she can decline.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[David is in a position of power over Jessie and can influence the decision to promote her. These factors could pressure Jessie to accept David's request.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="3" points="-1">
			<advice><![CDATA[David has not made any inappropriate comments toward Jessie. The exchanges they have shared do not seem problematic.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[While David may not have made harassing comments, his request may pressure Jessie into accepting the date. His behavior could be viewed as quid pro quo because he is considering Jessie for a promotion.]]></hint>
		</advisor>
		<advisor id="4" points="1">
			<advice><![CDATA[David appears to be leveraging his position over Jessie but it is a bit too early to tell. Jessie should probably go to the dinner but the situation should be watched.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[David appears to be using his power to gain romantic or sexual favors, which is a form of sexual harassment.  If David wants to get to know Jessie better, he can offer a lunch during work hours and not at a romantic location.]]></hint>
</advisor>
	</scenario>


  <scenario id="5">
    <background><![CDATA[<span style="display:block;font-size:23px;line-height:1.1">Charlotte has recently been promoted to work on Jeff's team.  Jeff has found that he has increasingly needed to work one on one with Charlotte. Charlotte is very attractive and everyone knows that Jeff is recently divorced. With all the talk about #METOO and men being accused of inappropriate behavior, Jeff is worried about how this new working relationship with Charlotte will look to the rest of the team and especially about being behind closed doors with Charlotte.  What should he do?</span>]]></background>
    <advisor id="1" points="1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should keep his office door open whenever he has one on one meetings with anyone.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[While this may make Jeff more comfortable and he will not be singling Charlotte out as a woman, open door discussions may not always be practical and should not be necessary if Jeff conducts himself in a professional manner with all of his colleagues. ]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="2" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should ask to have Charlotte transferred to another team to avoid any awkwardness.]]></advice>
      <hint><![CDATA[This could be seen as discrimination based on Charlotte's gender.]]></hint>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="3" points="2">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should treat Charlotte the same as all other team members including with respect to his meeting protocol.  He cannot let his worry about workplace gossip impact his business relationships. However, if he hears untrue rumors about his relationship with Charlotte, he can have these rumors investigated by reporting them internally.]]></advice>
    </advisor>
    <advisor id="4" points="-1">
      <advice><![CDATA[Jeff should call a team meeting and let everyone know that there is nothing romantic going on between him and Charlotte.]]></advice>
			<hint><![CDATA[This could be awkward for everyone, especially for Charlotte. ]]></hint>
    </advisor>
  </scenario>

	<feedback>
		<feedbacktitle><![CDATA[How did you do?]]></feedbacktitle>

		<low>
			<title1><![CDATA[You can do better.]]></title1>
			<page1><![CDATA[Based on the actions that you took (and did not take), here are some hints to guide you.
[INJECT]
When you are ready, click Try Again and take another look at these scenarios.]]></page1>
		</low>

		<medium>
			<title1><![CDATA[Nice Work!]]></title1>
			<page1><![CDATA[Based on the actions that you took (and did not take), here are the parts of the policy that you should carefully review.
		[INJECT]
		When you are ready, click Try Again and take another look at these scenarios. (Or, if you are satisfied with your rating, you could click Next.)]]></page1>
		</medium>

		<high>
			<title1><![CDATA[Excellent Work!]]></title1>
			<page1><![CDATA[Your competence in this area will go a long way toward creating a positive and inclusive work environment that is respectful and comfortable for everyone. You are a true role model in your organization.<br><br>Click Next to continue with this training.]]></page1>
		</high>

		<page background="img/22.jpg" x="0" y="-33" width="442" nextX="512">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[{TITLE}]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[{BODY 1}}]]></body>
		</page>
	</feedback>
	<outro>
		<page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="70" width="530" html="consider.html">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
		</page>



    <page background="SAME" x="0" y="100" width="615">
			<background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Remember...]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[As a supervisor, you are held to a heightened standard of behavior.
				<ul>
					<li>You are in a position of authority</li>
					<li>You are required to report any harassment that is reported to you or that you observe, even if no one is objecting to the harassment</li>
					<li>If you receive a report of, or are otherwise aware of, harassment you must promptly report it, even if you think the conduct is trivial or if the harassed individual asks you not to report it</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
		</page>

		<page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="93" width="850">
	      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
	      <header><![CDATA[So What's at Stake if You Don't Make the Right Decisions?]]></header>
	      <body>
	        <![CDATA[If you engage in sexual harassment or fail to follow your Organziation's anti-harassment and discrimination policy, your conduct could result in...<br><ul>
					<li>Discipline, up to and including termination</li>
	        <li>Damage to culture of inclusion and equal opportunities</li>
					<li>Loss of Organziation reputation</li>
					<li>Loss of your professional and personal reputation</li>
	        <li>Civil penalties</li>
					<li>Legal fees</li>
					<li>Monetary judgments</li>
	        <li>Criminal penalties</li>
					<li>Business interruptions and distractions leading to decreased employee engagement</li>
				</ul>]]>
	      </body>
	   </page>
	   <!--
	    <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="120" width="570" height="300">
			<background scale="0.63" x="-335" y="-220" animate="true"/>
			<header><![CDATA[]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[Let's take a look at one more scenario that will give you a chance to put your knowledge into action.
				<br><br>
			To progress through the scenario choose the box with the statment or question that best reflects your initial reaction to the situation described.]]></body>
		</page> -->
		<page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="362" y="200" width="638" heightOffset="220">
            <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
            <header><![CDATA[]]></header>
            <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a better understanding of terminology and the types of protections afforded to transgender employees, let's take a look at one more scenario that will give you a chance to put your knowledge into practice.]]></body>
        </page>
        <!-- <page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="362" y="200" width="638" heightOffset="220">
            <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
            <header><![CDATA[]]></header>
            <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a good sense for what types of behaviours consititute sexual harassment, let's examine one more situation.]]></body>
        </page> -->
        
	</outro>

	<outro1>
		<!-- <page background="img/12.jpg" x="500" y="82" width="530" heightOffset="220">
            <background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
            <header><![CDATA[]]></header>
            <body><![CDATA[Now that you have a good sense for what types of behaviors consititute sexual harassment, let's examine one more situation.]]></body>
        </page> -->
	</outro1>
	<outro2>

		<page background="img/sexual_har_outro.jpg" x="0" y="93" width="850">
	      <background scale="0.7" x="-335" y="-220" animate="false"/>
	      <header><![CDATA[So What's at Stake if You Don't Make the Right Decisions? FOR ALLEN DEVELOPMENT]]></header>
	      <body>
	        <![CDATA[If you engage in sexual harassment or fail to follow your organization's anti-harassment and discrimination policy, your conduct could result in...<br><ul>
					<li>Discipline, up to and including termination</li>
	        <li>Damage to culture of inclusion and equal opportunities</li>
					<li>Loss of organization reputation</li>
					<li>Loss of your professional and personal reputation</li>
	        <li>Civil penalties</li>
					<li>Legal fees</li>
					<li>Monetary judgments</li>
	        <li>Criminal penalties</li>
					<li>Business interruptions and distractions leading to decreased employee engagement</li>
				</ul>]]>
	      </body>
	   </page>

	    <page background="img/17.jpg" x="0" y="45" width="464">
			<background scale="1" x="0" y="0" animate="false"/>
			<header><![CDATA[Remember...]]></header>
			<body><![CDATA[As a supervisor, you are held to a heightened standard of behavior.
				<ul>
					<li>You are in a position of authority</li>
					<li>You are required to report any harassment that is reported to you or that you observe, even if no one is objecting to the harassment</li>
					<li>If you receive a report of, or are otherwise aware of, harassment you must promptly report it, even if you think the conduct is trivial or if the harassed individual asks you not to report it</li>
			</ul>]]></body>
		</page>
		
	</outro2>
</harassment>